rankjunction.com 2019-09-27

# TermsAndConditions | RankJunction

RankJunction.com is committed to privacy of information received through the website or the equivalent RankJunction Mobile Application available on Google Play from visitors, however, by using this website or RankJunction App, it is implied that the visitors consent to the terms contained herein. RankJunction.com follows the following procedures to safeguard the privacy of visitors to its websites.

We limit visit data collection to Browser Type, Page Accessed, Visit Duration, IP Address and Cookies. This keeps the visitor to the website anonymous. 

Personally identifiable information like Name, Address, Telephone Nos., email Ids etc. is collected only if the visitor volunteers to provide it by registering on RankJunction.com or RankJunction App or on requesting information from RankJunction.com, the information shall be used only for sending information requested / subscribed for by the visitor. Personally identifiable information may be disclosed for the following reasons:

  * To third parties in connection with visitor's purchase of third parties products or services from RankJunction.com or RankJunction App.
  * In the event of a corporate re-organization, it may be required to pass on such information to the surviving entity.
  * In the event disclosure of information is required by Law, a Regulation, National Security or a Government agency.
  * Information disclosed in message boards or forums are in public space hence visitors need to exercise restraint, because in this space everything is public information.

RankJunction.com shall not be responsible for privacy policies (Present and Future) of other websites to which links may be provided in RankJunction.com Website. Neither shall RankJunction.com be responsible for the content or any unsolicited communication from any of the other Websites to which links may be provided on the RankJunction.com Website. 

RankJunction.com reserves the right to change the privacy policy at any point in with or without notice. The revised privacy policy shall be posted on the website. A visitors use of the website shall be subject to the currently prevailing privacy policy. 

Visitors to RankJunction.com Website are free to unsubscribe to any Information / Communication from RankJunction.com anytime.

Visitors may contact RankJunction.com at Contact@Rankjunction.com for any query regarding the privacy policy of the Website or The Company. Visitors may also update their personally identifiable information here.
